练习 1-34：形容词和动词的规则转换。根据词性标出语调，
Exercise 1-34, Regular Transitions of Adjectives and Verbs Mark the intonation
或标出粗体词的长元音，并标出正确音节。
or indicate the long vowel on the bold-faced word, depending on which part of
按词性标出正确音节；下面从第一题开始。
speech it is. Mark the proper syllables. 1. You need to insert a paragraph here on
this newspaper insert. 2. How can you object to this object? 3. I'd like to
present you with this present. 4. Would you care to elaborate on his elaborate
explanation? 5. The manufacturer couldn't recall if there'd been a recall. 6. The
religious convert wanted to convert the world. 7. The political rebels wanted to
rebel against the world. 8. The mogul wanted to record a new record for his
latest artist. 9. If you perfect your intonation, your accent will be perfect.
10. Due to the drought, the fields didn't produce much produce this year. 11.
Unfortunately, City Hall wouldn't permit them to get a permit. 12. Have you heard
that your associate is known to associate with gangsters? 13. How much do you
estimate that the estimate will be? 14. The facilitator wanted to separate the
general topic into separate categories.